JT

# JONAH TUCKMAN

jtuckman9@gmail.com | (609) 731-8539 | New York, United States 11211

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Proven Founder and CEO in the Tech Space.

While still in college, **built a Blockchain Consulting firm that was later acquired**, and **founded a startup in the Mobile Ad-Tech space** that I raised \$400,000 to build. Spent the last two and a half years building and bringing to market this startup which has now been market-released and revenue generating in the New York Market. Worked with some of the largest businesses in the Ad-Tech space, billion-dollar manufacturers in Eastern Asia, and reputable investment funds. Managed a team of 15 people to build and create a market-accepted product.

## ACCOMPLISHME NTS

- Featured in Yahoo Finance, Market Watch and Seeking Alpha
- Multiple Keynote Speeches to the Vassar College Business Club
- Vassar College Newspaper Podcast Interview

#### SKILLS

- Leadership
- To-Market Planning
- Problem Solving
- Product Development
- Product Demonstrations
- Decision Making
- Business Operations

- Strategy Planning
- Staff Management
- Budget Control
- Cost Analysis
- Business Development
- Financial Data interpretation

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Founder & CEO | EBumps - New York, NY

11/2019 - CURRENT

- Built eBumps from a concept to a fully developed, funded, and market released revenue-generating platform.
- Brokered dozens of partnerships within the ad-tech space, needed for the general functionality of the system, the product sales, and various businesses in the space.
- Brokered deal with a billion dollar East-Asian manufacturer to design and build our screens then coordinated shipping and installation.
- Raised over half a million dollars in multiple pre-seed funding rounds domestically and have signed LOIs with investment houses in Singapore about international expansion.
- Led the development teams in the design and functional building of the product, oversaw outsourced marketing teams, led sales pushes,

**brokered partnerships** in the space, coordinated conversations with our legal team and more.

**Director Of Technology** | Fitzner Blockchain 02/2019 - 11/2019 Consulting, LLC - Poughkeepsie, NY

- Provided concept-design solutions, resource management and general advisory to a variety of companies and projects in the Blockchain space.
- Worked with companies to provide solutions to complex problems by utilizing the core principles of **blockchain technolog**y within their business model.
- Designed and oversaw technical development for clients as well as designed internal business models and to-market strategies for companies early in their formation.
- Was one of the original four members at the firm. The business was eventually sold for a six-figure sum.

**Software Engineering Intern** | Raycatch - Al Diagnostics for Solar Energy - Tel Aviv, Israel

04/2019 - 08/2019

- Worked on DeepSolar software that utilized state-of-the-art artificial intelligence technology to maximize plant ROI in large solar fields.
- Analyzed existing data, identified insights and quantified how they will affect our clients profitability, thereby increasing energy yield, reducing expenditure and improving ROI.
- Developed a close **relationship with the company's Chairman**, who retained me for many consulting jobs for the various companies he was invested in.

#### **EDUCATION**

Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, NY

**Bachelor of Arts**: Computer Science and Mathematics